{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
老佛爷lfy\h\h\h\h\h哈哈哈是奇\h\h\h\h天天想吃柚子
粲呀粲\h\h\hmemdaak
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
Junosis\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
大红
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
吞咽
请注意  请注意一下
Attention, please. Your attention, please.
我也不想打断你们享受羊肉和赤霞珠红酒
Um, I hate to pull you away from your lamb and cabernet
我只想快点宣布一下
but I just want to make a quick announcement
关于我儿子里奇
about my son, Richie.
今晚  我们要任命他成为我们公司
Tonight, we are making him the youngest managing director
历史上最年轻的总经理
in the history of our little company.
做得好  孩子  这是你应得的
Well done, kiddo. You earned it.
做得好  来吧  站起来  里奇
Well done. Come on. Stand up, Richie.
来吧  上去吧
Come on. Get up there.
我  如果没有我美丽的新娘亨特
You know, I -- I couldn't have done any of this
我不可能做到这样
without my beautiful bride, Hunter.
她是  一直是
She is, and has been,
如此的无私奉献
so giving, selfless..
她是我生命中的光芒
Well, she is the light of my life.
还有我父母给我们买了房子
Oh, uh, my folks bought us a house
所以非常感谢提供房子
so thank you very much for the house.
令你容光焕发  无忧无虑  精神振奋
You're radiant, you're blessed, you're inspiring.
使用奥拉丁新品
Keep on shining with new Oradine
美白牙膏和牙贴继保持牙齿闪耀
Whitening Toothpaste and teeth strips.
我们的搪瓷保护技术让您
Our enamel protection technology allows you
想吃什么就吃什么  笑口常开
to eat whatever you want and keep smiling.
奥拉丁
Oradine.
瞧瞧你
Wow! Look at you!
你想我了吗
Did you miss me?
太棒了
This is great.
我觉得后院泳池附近
I think there's room for a flower bed out back..
还有地方放个花坛
...near the pool.
如果可以的话  我想种一些花
I'd like to plant some if that's okay.
是吗  什么花
Oh, yeah? What kind of flowers?
卷丹  郁金香  牵牛花
Tiger Lilies, Tulips, Morning Glories.
对不起  宝贝  等一下
Sorry, babe. One second.
-我得回复一下  -好吧  没事
- I just gotta respond to this. - Okay. Sure.
这花的名字真棒  是吧
It's a great name for a flower, isn't it?
牵牛花[早晨的荣耀]
Morning Glories.
就像是赞颂美好早晨
Like the glory of an awesome morning.
我越来越喜欢早晨了
I like mornings more and more these days.
这房子光照很好
This house has great light.
我觉得很幸运
I feel so lucky.
妈  我们有喜了
Ma, we're pregnant.
对啊
Yeah.
对
Yes.
我知道
I know.
我会的
I will.
就是
Just..
我们来了
There we are.
亲爱的  多美好的一天
Darling, what a day!
-是啊  是啊  真有趣  -好消息
- Yeah, yeah, this is fun. - Good news!
-嗨  甜心  -你好
- Hi, sweetheart. - Hi.
瞧瞧这
Look at this.
我们公司未来的首席执行官  就在这里
The future CEO of our company, right here.
就在这里
Right here.
我生里奇阵痛了30个小时
I was in labor for 30 hours with Richie.
他不想出来  他在里面折腾
He didn't wanna come out. He had it made in there.
三十小时  然后  他出生时脸色发青
Thirty hours. And then, he was born blue.
-发青  -面如死灰
- Blue? - Slate blue.
我们都以为他死了
We all thought he was dead
但后来他开始呼吸然后会爬
but then he started breathing and crawling.
还吸猫的尾巴
And sucking on the cat's tail.
-什么  -是的  对
- What? - Yes. Yes.
显然  比起我的奶嘴  我更喜欢猫的尾巴
Uh, apparently, I prefer the cat's tail to my pacifier.
猫的尾巴总是湿的
The cat's tail was always wet.
亨特也是个疯小孩
You know, Hunter was a crazy kid, too.
告诉他们  那什么
Tell them about the, uh.. What was it?
路边那个谁
The -- the guy on the side of the road who, uh..
-对啊  对啊  说出来  -不是这样的
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Tell it. - That's not --
说吧  很好  很好
Do it. It's good. It's good.
来吧
Come on.
太棒了
This is great.
这真的不算故事
It's not really a story.
有个家伙
Um, there was this guy
有点像酒吧疯子
kind of this local nutcase
他会站在进城的路边
and he would stand on the side of the road
然后他会飞吻给
into town and he would blow kisses
所有经过的车
at all the cars passing by.
一开始  他吓到我了
And at first, he scared me
因为他有胡子
because he had this beard
还有脏头发和坏牙齿
and dirty hair and bad teeth.
就像是邪教打扮之类的
Uh, it was like this religious calling or something.
-他不得不吹  -对了  里奇
- He had to blow -- - Oh, by the way, Richie..
我差点忘了  卡弗的人怎么样了
Uh, before I forget, um, how was it left with the Carver people?
他们把合同发过来了  在用电子签名
They sent over the contracts and it's being e-signed
因为其中一个伙伴在非洲
because one of the partners is in Africa
去旅行之类的
on a safari or something like that.
什么时候  我不知道  我不清楚
As of when? I didn't know. I wasn't aware of this.
-看起来  他带了孩子  -真的吗
- Apparently, he took the kid. - Really?
-他去  -那我不知道
- There he is.. - I didn't know about that.
成交了
Closing the deal.
好吧  要跟进这些事情
Alright. Gotta keep up on these things.
我  我会  会给他发邮件  星期一就发
Yeah, I -- I'll -- I'll email him f -- first thing Monday.
-好吧  很好  -我马上去
- Okay. Good. - I'll get right on it.
他在旅行  真的
He's on safari. No, really.
如果他在旅行的话
Oh, oh, well, if he's on safari --
-不  我是认真的  我是认真的  -我知道
- No, I mean it. I mean it. - I know.
-好吧  好吧  -但他出去了
- Okay, fine. - But he's, I mean, he's out..
你又没上网
It's not like you get internet.
在撒哈拉沙漠
...the Sahara somewhere.
没事的  我不在乎
It's fine. I don't care.
我觉得没什么好担心的
I don't think there's anything to worry about.
对不起
Sorry.
这冰太棒了
This ice is totally awesome. Mm!
对不起  亲爱的
Sorry, darling.
我自己进来了
I let myself in.
-你吓到我了  -很明显
- You gave me such a fright. - Obviously.
我只是想把这个带过来
I just wanted to bring this over.
自助书
Self-help book.
我怀孕的时候读的
I read it when I was pregnant
这对产后真的很有帮助
and it really helped with the postpartum.
天啊  我喜欢
Oh, my gosh. I love it.
我在做午饭
I'm making lunch.
烤奶酪三明治和番茄汤
Grilled cheese sandwiches and tomato soup.
你能留下来吗
Can you stay?
-我也希望我能  -我还可以做点别的
- I wish I could. - I can make something else.
不  不  不  别麻烦了  我得走了
No, no, no. Don't bother. I better be going.
你留着长发会很漂亮的
You would look so pretty with long hair.
你应该把它留长
You should grow it out.
里奇喜欢留着又长又漂亮头发的姑娘们
Richie likes his girls with long, beautiful hair.
《快乐的天赋》
每天  试着做一些意想不到的事
强迫自己尝试新事物
什么事情这么高兴
What are you so happy about?
我为自己感到骄傲
I'm proud of myself.
我今天做了件意想不到的事
I did something unexpected today.
什么
What?
你保证如果我告诉你你不会笑我吗
You promise you won't laugh if I tell you?
保证我不会笑
Promise I won't laugh.
窗帘
the drapes
我为剧院选了天蓝色的窗帘
I chose sky blue drapes for the theater.
那挺好啊
Oh. Cool.
但这并不意外
That's not so unexpected.
你确定那是合适的颜色吗
You sure that's the right color, though?
有点时髦
It's a little hipster.
我觉得它管用
I think it works.
你说可以任我选
And you said that I could choose.
是的  你可以  你当然可以
I did. And you can. Of course you can.
你来决定  我喜欢意外点
It's up to you. I like unexpected.
过来
Come here.
我能让你开心吗
Do I make you happy?
我是全世界最开心的人
I'm the happiest man in the whole world.
我爱你的一切  每一件小事
I love everything about you. Every little thing.
你没生我的气吗
You're not mad at me?
关于什么  窗帘吗
About what? The drapes?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只是想确定我没有做错什么
I just wanna make sure I'm not doing anything wrong.
你没有
You're not.
即使你故意去
You couldn't do anything wrong
你都不会做错的
even if you tried.
好吧  好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
宝贝
Babe?
宝贝  你把领带熨了吗
Babe, did you iron this tie?
是啊
Yeah.
它皱了
It was wrinkled.
你不能熨这领带
You can't iron a tie like this.
会永久的损坏丝绸
It'll permanently damage the silk.
只能蒸熨
It has to be steamed.
你看到了吗
You see?
天啊  我很抱歉
Oh, shoot. I'm sorry.
你还有领带可以用吗
Do you have another tie you can wear?
没有配这衬衫的
Not one that goes with this shirt.
操
Fuck.
现在我该怎么办
Now what the hell am I gonna do?
没事的
It's okay.
新的医学证据表明
New Medical evidence suggests that
产后吃胎盘
consuming your placenta after giving birth
可以降低荷尔蒙  增加产奶量
can level off your hormones, increase milk production
降低产后抑郁的几率
and lower chances of postpartum depression.
你的胎盘可以被干燥并加工
Your placenta can be dried out and converted
变成日常饮食补充
into daily dietary supplements.
你好
Hi!
是
Yeah.
我马上过去
I'll be right over!
再见
Bye.
很好  棒极了
Good. Great.
我也想成为一名艺术家
I wanted to be an artist too, you know.
真的吗
Really?
当演员
Well, an actress.
我看得出来  你真是个天才
I could see that. You're a knockout.
谢谢你  你也是
Thank you. So are you.
谢谢您
Thank you.
你在遇见我儿子之前都做些什么
So what did you do for money before you met my son?
主要是做零售
Retail, mostly.
-在店里卖东西吗  -对
- Selling things in a shop? - Yeah.
卖什么
Selling what?
洗漱用品
Toiletries.
泡泡浴液  沐浴乳
Bubble bath, body wash.
肥皂
Soap.
幸运的是你遇到了我的儿子
Well, lucky break you meeting my son.
是啊
Yeah.
我还做些插画的工作
I would go to these illustration job, um..
参加广告的面试
...advertising interviews
反正他们也不见得会雇我
and, and it wasn't like they were gonna hire me anyway.
我真的很感激
I'm just real grateful..
里奇和你们
...to Richie and you guys
给我提供了足够自立的资本
for providing me some solid ground to stand on, you know?
而且我现在有很多空闲时间了
Plus I have so much free time now
用来画画什么的
for drawing and whatever.
别人给过我最好的建议是
The best advice anyone ever gave me was
假装能做到  直到真的做到了为止
"Fake it till you make it."
你是假装能做到  还是真的做到了
Are you a faker or have you made it?
抱歉  你说什么
I'm sorry?
你是真的开心  还是装作开心
Are you happy or are you pretending to be happy?
我是真的开心
I'm happy.
你们这是在干嘛
What's going on?
不不不  我是在
No, no, no. No, no, I was..
你想让我们相信你到底有多醉吗
Are you trying to convince us how drunk you actually are?
-我来吧  -我非常清醒
- I got this. - I'm as sober as long as a..
幸好是我把你载过来的
Good thing I was the one to drive you over..
-太火辣了  兄弟  -进去吧  兄弟
- Yeah, man. So sexy! - Yeah, get in there, my man.
进去吧
Let's go.
等一下
Just a minute!
宝贝  你在里面干什么
Hey, babe? What's going on in there?
怎么了
What?
出什么事了  你在发抖
What's wrong? You're trembling.
没事  我很好
Nothing. I'm okay.
-我马上就下去  -好
- I'll be right down. - Okay.
-绝不可能  绝不可能  -快出来
- Not a chance. Not a chance. - Get out of here.
不可能  不可能  你要蹲局子了
No way. No way. You're in cuffs.
你连酒精检测仪都不需要
You don't even need a breathalyzer.
你要蹲局子了  你完了  你完了
You're in cuffs. You're done. You're done.
下一个是谁  下一个是谁
Who's up next? Who's up next?
就像  就像回到了新兵训练营
Just like, just like you're back in boot camp there.
出什么事了
What happened?
-什么  -你衣服湿了
- What? - You're damp.
是的  抱歉
Yeah. Sorry.
我是亚伦  我是理查德的同事
Yeah, I'm Aaron. I work with Richard.
我是亨特  我是理查德的妻子
I'm Hunter. I'm married to Richard.
恭喜
Congratulations.
-恭喜什么  -宝宝
- For what? - The baby.
也是
Oh. Yeah.
你能给我个拥抱吗
Hey, can I have a hug?
-什么  -一个拥抱
- What? - A -- a hug.
你  你能抱我一下吗
W -- will you hug me?
为什么
Why?
因为我还没醉到让你亲我的地步
Because I'm not drunk enough to ask for a kiss.
-我是里奇的妻子  记得吗  -只是
- I'm Richie's wife, remember? - So, it's..
只是一个拥抱
It's just a hug.
一个拥抱  亲爱的
One hug, hon.
我很孤单
I'm lonely.
好吧  抱一个
Okay, come here.
-谢谢你  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
准备好了吗
Ready?
看啊
Oh, look at that.
看上去里面有别的东西
It looks like there's something else inside there.
-什么  -你什么意思
- What? - What do you mean?
就是一个小故障  我移一下
It's just a glitch. Let me move the --
里奇  里奇
Richie! Richie!
-里奇  你在哪儿  -我在
- Richie, where are you? - I'm..
-完全没必要  我没事  -我  我就在这里
- This isn't necessary! I'm fine! - I'm -- I'm right here!
-我没事  -亨特  我就在这里
- I'm fine! - Hunter, I'm right here!
你脑子有什么毛病
What is wrong with you? Huh?
说真的  说真的  我试着理解过了
Really. Really. I -- I am trying to understand, alright?
为什么  为什么  你为什么要干这种事
Why? Why? Why would you do something like this?
你他妈脑子有什么毛病
I mean, what the fuck is wrong with you?
-我不知道  -你很清楚
- I don't know. - You do.
我不知道
I don't know.
我就是
I just..
我有这股冲动  就这么干了
I wanted to do it, and so I did it.
真是个好借口
Oh, that's a great excuse.
我以前从没听说过异食癖这玩意
I've never even heard of this pica thing.
-你别越吼越大声了  -你知道吗
- Just stop raising your voice! - You know what?
这种事是你结婚前
This is the kind of thing that you're supposed to tell
本应该告知对方的
somebody about before you get married.
你本应该告诉我的
You should've told me about this.
我压根不知道
I didn't know about it!
放屁  亨特
Oh, that's such bullshit, Hunter!
别他妈用这种谎来骗我
Alright? Don't fucking lie to me like that!
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我之前从没做过这种事
I've never done anything like this before.
我  我忍不住
I can't, I can't help it.
靠  该死
Shit! Damn it!
你他妈脑子有什么毛病
Just what the fuck is wrong with you?
这些傻逼石头
These stupid fucking rocks.
当然了  所有东西花的都是我的钱
Yeah, sure. Just have me fucking paying for everything.
没关系  你不知道原因
That's fine. You don't know why.
因为你整天待在家里
No, you're just sitting here at home all day
做剪贴簿  挑你妈的窗帘
making scrapbooks and picking out fucking curtains.
要我说先使用药物治疗  不是吗  爱丽丝
Well, I would think medication first, right, Alice?
先把她稳定下来
I mean, just to settle her down.
我不想对你的工作指手画脚
I don't wanna tell you how to do your job
但我付了钱  就要出效果
but I am paying for this, so results.
我们要的是效果
We want results.
我最好能和亨特单独聊一聊
I think it might be better if I met with Hunter alone for a bit.
不  不行  我要留下来
Ah, no. No, I -- I'm gonna stay.
为了确保她
Yeah, just to make sure that she's..
我没事的  真的
I'm okay. Really.
-好吧  -那好
- Alright. - Okay.
我们就在外面
We'll be right outside.
你想躺下吗
Do you want to lie down?
能就  药物治疗吗
Can I just...have the medication?
当然可以试试西普兰  或者安非他酮
We can try Celexa or -- or Wellbutrin. Sure.
均为抗抑郁药物
但谈话治疗也很重要
But talking is important, too.
你想谈谈你的父母吗
Are you reluctant to talk about your parents?
完全是浪费时间
It's just a waste of time.
他们对我很好
They were good to me.
我的童年很普通
I had a normal childhood.
我家人非常爱我  没别的了
My family loved me very much. End of story.
我只想别再乱吃东西  好让里奇开心
I just wanna stop eating stuff so I can make Richie happy
然后让生活回归正常
and we can go back to our life together.
你吞东西的时候什么感觉
How does it make you feel when you swallow something?
我不知道
I don't know.
好像感觉很棒
Good, I guess.
在什么方面
In what way?
我喜欢在我嘴里的触感
I just like the textures in my mouth.
我喜欢它们在我嘴里的感觉
I like the way they feel in my mouth.
床垫芯
Mattress stuffing..
冰块  金属  特别是冷的金属
...ice, metal cold metal, especially.
就那种玩意儿
Junk like that.
痛感对你有什么困扰吗
Does the pain bother you?
你吞咽的一些物品  相当尖锐
Some of the objects you swallowed are, are quite sharp.
好了  开始榨汁
Okay. Let's start juicing.
我们要每天给你做一杯
We're gonna make you a daily
富含铁元素的水果蔬菜汁
fruit and vegetable drink with lots of iron.
你的大脑和身体是相连的
You see, your brain and your body are connected.
但现在  你的身体很饥饿
But right now,your body's starving
所以给大脑传错了
so it is sending the wrong signal to the brain
想吃什么东西的信号
about what it wants to eat.
所以  我们要给大脑和身体重新建立连接
So we are going to reconnect the mind and the body.
当然了
Yeah. Totally.
Totally.
宝贝
Hey, babe.
我要耽误你一下会儿
I'm gonna steal you for a second.
-我们在榨汁呢  -是的
- We're juicing. - Oh, yeah.
我想让你见个人
There's somebody I want you to meet.
-来吧  -我马上回来
- Come on. - I'll be right back.
-好  -来吧
- Okay. - Come on.
-是谁啊  -一会就知道了
- Who is it? - Oh, you'll see.
他就在楼下
He's just downstairs.
你好  很高兴见到你  我是路埃
Hi. Nice to meet you. I'm Luay.
-你好  路易  -是路埃
- Hi, Louie. - Luay.
他是谁
Who is he?
路埃会在家里给你搭把手
Luay's gonna be helping you out around the house.
他是个护士  住家护士
He's a nurse. A live-in nurse.
他把姥姥照顾得很好  很贴心
He's great with memaw. Very sensitive.
具体要干什么
Doing what, exactly?
我又不是老年人
I'm not a senior citizen.
听着  我得工作  不能24小时待在家里
Look, I gotta work. I can't be here 24/7.
所以他是来监视我的吗
So he's here to keep an eye on me?
不  他是来帮忙的
No, he's here as a resource.
如果你累了  他能给你做饭
If you're tired, he can cook for you.
他能去商店给你买东西
He can go to the store and get you things.
什么  他会把东西从我手里拿出来吗
What, is he gonna be pulling stuff out of my hands?
没事  没事的  放轻松  宝贝  好吗
Okay, okay. Just relax, babe, okay?
妈妈  妈妈  你能来解释一下这事吗
Mom? Mom, can you come and explain this, please?
这是你的主意  我现在说不明白这个
This was your idea and I just...can't deal with this right now.
我怀孕的时候  得到了邻里的帮助
You know, I had help around the house when I was pregnant.
这真的帮我减轻了压力
It really takes the pressure off.
再加上  你刚刚出院
Plus, you're still recovering
还处于恢复阶段
from your little stay in the hospital.
亲爱的  路埃是这最好的看护了
Honey, Luay is the best there is.
帮我们  也是帮你
Help us help you.
我自己可以
Oh, I can do it.
I can do it!
里奇先生让我帮你
Mr. Richie wants me to help you.
我能做好顿饭
I can cook just fine.
我想亲自给我丈夫做晚餐
I wanna cook my husband's dinner by myself.
你去看电视或干点别的去吧
Go watch TV or something.
拜托了
Please.
你是哪里人
So where are you from?
大马士革
Damascus.
是叙利亚  不是匹兹堡
Syria, not Pittsburgh.
那你为什么离开了呢
Why'd you leave?
因为战乱
War.
那你是哪里人
Where are you from?
在梅雷迪思的东部  纽约的北部
East Meredith. Upstate New York.
那里没有战争
No war there.
只有些树啊牛啊农场啊之类的
Just trees and cows and farms and stuff.
如果你处于战乱之中
If you were in war,
你就不会得这种心理疾病了
you would not have this problem of the mind.
当你可能被枪杀的时候
No time for mind problems
你是没时间烦恼的
when you're being shot at.
我得去上厕所
I have to go to the bathroom now.
别让我为难  小姐
Please, miss.
你知道他们的要求的  好吗
You know what they want, okay?
我必须这么做
You know what I'm supposed to do.
好了  去吧
Okay, go.
医院把你的报告送来了
The hospital sent over a report
详细的说明了你胃里有什么东西
detailing the contents of your stomach.
上面写了你吞了一块电池
It said you swallowed a battery.
这没什么大不了的
It's just so not a big deal.
但是所有人都在为这件事费尽心思
Everyone is making a big deal about it.
对  我确实做了不该做的事
Yes, I did some things that I shouldn't have.
电池似乎就是个大问题
Well, a battery seems like a big deal.
如果它在你胃里泄漏
If it leaked inside your stomach
那些强酸会要了你的命的
the acid could've killed you.
那让我很担心
That concerns me.
一根针  一块石头  一个电池
A needle, a rock, a battery.
为什么要吃这些东西呢
Why those objects?
我不知道
I don't know.
只是让我感觉
It made me feel..
我能掌控一切
...in control.
你觉得自己失控了吗
Do you feel out of control?
有点事
Oh, um, there was something
我得告诉你  关于
that I wanted to tell you about, um..
我妈妈以及我们之间的关系之类的的事
...my mom and our relationship and stuff.
你知道吗  还是算了吧
You know what? Never mind.
亨特
Hunter.
今天是里奇的生日  我真的得赶紧去了
It's Richie's birthday. I really have to go.
拜拜
Bye.
-你好啊 寿星小伙  -你好  宝贝
- Hi, birthday boy. - Hi, babe.
你好  亨特  派对不错哦
Hi, Hunter. Great party.
你好  萨拉  最近怎么样
Hi, Sara. How are you?
派对很棒的哦
Great party.
-你好啊  劳伦  -你好
- Hi, Lauren. - Hi.
-我喜欢你这条裙子  -亨特
- I love your dress. - Hunter..
你为这派对做的事都太棒了
I love what you've done with the place.
看看这些三明治  它们真有意思
Look at these sandwiches. They're hilarious.
-来一个  -不了不了不了  把它们拿远点
- Have one. - Oh, no, no, no. Get those away from me.
我还吃的话估计得去洗胃了
If I eat anymore I'm gonna have to get my stomach pumped.
老天  亨特
Oh, my God. Hunter.
甜心  对不起  我不应该
Sweetie, I'm so sorry. I didn't..
-我就是傻瓜  我不该  -什么
- I'm such an idiot. I didn't.. - What?
我说话没过脑子  我只是
I wasn't even thinking, and I just --
别  别  别  贝夫  贝夫
No, no, no. Bev, Bev.
别太  别太担心这个
Don't even, don't even worry about it.
没事  没什么的  真的  没事
It's fine. It's fine. Really, it's okay.
我们都挺好的
And we're doing great.
是的  亨特的情况改善了很多了
Yeah, H -- Hunter's made a lot of progress, and..
好吧
Right.
我妈妈已经为她制定了新的食谱
My mom's got her on a new diet.
-对吧  -什么样的食谱
- Right? - Mm. What diet?
富含铁和纤维
Lots of...iron and fiber.
-很健康呢  -还有鱼和
- Mm. That's so healthy. - And fish and --
-很好  -很好   不错  是的
- Right. - Right, right. Yeah.
-你看起来气色不错  -不是吗
- You look great. - Doesn't she?
-我爱这样的饮食  -是的  都是我的最爱
- I know. I love diets. - Yeah. She made all my favorites.
是的
Yeah.
我不希望有人知道
I'd rather no one know.
你生我气了吗
Well.. Are you mad at me?
这的所有人都在乎  非常在乎
Hon, e -- everybody here cares. They care big time.
你的食物可是个大焦点  是个超大的热点
Y -- your food's a big hit. It's a huge hit.
你应该感到开心啊
You should be happy about that.
是吧
Yeah.
我不敢相信你他妈的告诉他们了
I can't believe you fucking told them.
好吧  那你能不能不要破坏我的生日聚会
Okay, can you please not ruin my birthday?
我们之后在谈
We'll talk about this later.
你好
Hey.
我能不能
Can I, uh..
能不能抱你一下
Can I have a hug?
我很孤单
I'm lonely.
你还好吗  小姐
Are you okay, miss?
还好  谢谢关心
Yes, thank you.
好吧
Okay.
如果你想要什么就跟我说
Let me know if you need anything.
我就在外面
I -- I'll be right outside.
我还没好
I didn't finish.
向我道歉
Say you're sorry..
在派对上
...for the party..
告诉在那的所有人
...telling everyone at the office.
对不起  我很抱歉  宝贝
I'm sorry. I am, honey.
这对我来说也不容易
This hasn't been easy on me, either.
我需要支持
I needed the support.
你是不是无条件爱我的
Do you still love me unconditionally?
当然是
Of course.
是的
Yes.
是的  我无条件爱你
Yes, I do.
我会更努力去理解你
And I'm gonna try harder to understand
变的更加善解人意
to be more understanding.
好
Okay.
我也爱你
I love you too.
我很抱歉  我是个怪物
I'm sorry I'm such a freak.
那也是我的怪物
But you're my freak.
你是我的小怪物
You're my little freak.
让我们再谈谈你的家人
Let's get back to your family for a minute.
为什么
Why?
我跟你说过他们很正常
I told you they were normal.
上次谈话的时候  你暗示了你妈妈的
In last session, you hinted at some type of
一些问题
issue with your mom.
天呐
Oh, gosh.
我想你是想让我告诉你强奸的事情
I guess you want me to tell you about the whole rape thing.
什么强奸的事情
What whole rape thing?
好吧
Okay.
如果我告诉你  如果
If I tell you...if..
你得必须保证
...you have to promise
你不会大作文章
that you're not gonna make a big deal about it.
我保证
I promise.
我父亲不是我的亲生父亲
So my father isn't really my father.
我妈妈在90年代时被一个陌生人强奸了
My mom was raped in the '90s by some random guy
我就是那次强奸的结果  明白了吗
and I was the result, you know?
他们有没有抓到那家伙
Did they ever catch the guy?
有  花了不少时间
Yeah. He did time.
威廉·欧文是那时他的名字
William Erwin was his name
就是他的名字
is his name.
你想看他的照片吗
Do you wanna see a picture of him?
不用  不是很想
Oh, no. Not really.
没事  看吧
No, look.
看吧
Look.
这就是他
That's him.
你随身带着这照片吗
Y -- you carry that around with you?
是
Yeah.
我已经能接受了
I've dealt with it.
你是怎么接受的
How have you dealt with it?
我为此想了很多
I've thought about it a lot.
你妈妈有没有想过把你打掉
Did your mother ever consider terminating the pregnancy?
我妈妈是  很保守的右翼宗教信徒
My mom is...this right-wing religious nut.
她真的很好
She's really sweet.
我的家人从来不认为
My family doesn't believe in..
即使是在乱伦和强奸的情况下
...abortion even in the cases
要去堕胎
of incest or rape
所以有了我
so here I am.
不过我的继父对我很好
But my stepdad was really nice to me.
我妈妈也没有对这件事抱怨愤怒
And my mom was never resentful or anything.
我的姐妹们也很爱我
My sisters love me.
这件事是怎么发生的呢
How did it happen?
我妈妈去酒吧  然后他给她点了杯酒
She went to a bar and he bought her a drink.
我妈妈离开时
My mom left
他就跟踪她回家
and he followed her home
闯进了家里
and he broke in.
我知道只有这些了
That's all I know.
我们能谈点别的了吗
Can we change the subject?
事实上  这很重要
I think this is important, actually.
我想这可能与你的症状有很大关系
I think this might have a lot to do with your compulsion.
好吧
Okay.
我们的这次谈话要结束了
We're at the end of our session.
过几天再见
See you in a couple days.
你穿这个颜色很好看
That color looks really nice on you.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
回见
See you soon.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
过来
Come here.
真好看
Beautiful!
你好  我是理查德
Hello? This is Richard.
跟她的过去有关
...connected to her past.
跟她的过去有关是什么意思
What do you mean about her past?
我认为她的生活岌岌可危
I -- I think her life is in danger.
她没办法克服一些负罪感
She can't overcome a guilt complex
如果没有你的爱和包容
without your love and acceptance.
不  不  不  不  她的过去怎么了
No, no, no, no. What about her past?
拜托  你必须告诉我
Please, you have to tell me.
我不能说  去问她吧
I can't say. Just ask her.
听着  我们说好的  对吗
Listen, we had a deal, okay?
你应该把所有事都告诉我
You're supposed to tell me everything.
所有事
Everything.
如果你不说  我就不准她继续见你
If you won't tell me, I don't want her seeing you anymore.
和一次强奸有关
It has to do with a rape.
喂
Hello?
你还在听吗
Are you there?
喂
Hello?
在  我在听
No, I'm here.
所以  据我所知
So as I understand
亨特的父亲强奸了她母亲
Hunter's father raped her mother
她是这次犯罪的产物
and she is the product of that crime.
她跟你讲过这些吗
Did she say anything to you about this?
她提到过什么吗
Did she mention anything?
没  没有  我  我没听说过
No. No, I -- I didn't know.
不  我  我明白
No, I -- I understand.
原来你在这
Ah, there you are.
我要去健身房
I'm off to the gym.
我  我今天想给你买点东西
I'm -- I'm gonna get you something today.
你尽管提  想要  要裙子还是项链
Whatever you want. You want a -- a dress or necklace?
你来说  买给你的  什么都行
You name it, it's yours. Anything.
手链行吗
A bracelet?
手链  手链  好的
Bracelet. Bracelet. Oh, okay.
决定了
Done.
操
Oh, shit.
他妈的
Oh, fucking shit.
操他妈
Holy shit.
操
Shit.
亨特  你没事吧
Hunter? You alright?
我在床底下  走开
I'm under the bed. Go away.
你是不是不太舒服
You seem upset.
没有  操  大侦探
No shit, Sherlock.
请出来吧  你这样里奇先生会不高兴的
Please come out. Mr. Richie wouldn't like this.
我不
No.
这里好多灰
It's very dusty here.
我之后可能会打扫一下
Maybe I'll clean later.
我可能会打扫整个房间
Maybe I'll clean the whole room.
你在这很安全
You're safe here.
你很安全
You're safe.
小姐  小姐
Miss! Miss!
不  小姐
No. Miss.
♪ 幸福就像一只鸟 ♪
♪ Happiness is like a bird ♪
♪ 有二十只翅膀 ♪
♪ With 20 wings ♪
♪ 一抓就飞走 ♪
♪ Try to catch him as he flies ♪
♪ 幸福就像一只鸟 ♪
♪ Happiness is like a bird ♪
♪ 他的歌声 ♪
♪ That only sings ♪
♪ 只在空中起 ♪
♪ When his head is in the skies ♪
♪ 你能让他和你并排走 ♪
♪ You can try to make him walk beside you ♪
♪ 你能说大门自敞开 ♪
♪ You can say the door is open wide ♪
♪ 如果你抓他 ♪
♪ If you grab at him ♪
♪ 灾祸就来到 ♪
♪ Woe betide you ♪
♪ 我知道因为我抓过 ♪
♪ I know because I've tried ♪
我真的觉得这样不错
I really think it's a good idea.
只用在孩子出生前  去住一小段时间
Just for a little while until the baby is born.
亲爱的  你看
Sweetie, look.
这里很好吧  对吧
Look how nice this is, huh?
我们不能每分每秒都看着你  他们能
We can't keep our eyes on you 24/7, and they can.
我能留下  和里奇还有你们在一起吗
Can I stay here with Richie and you guys?
我现在好多了  真的  我好多了
I'm better now. Really, I am.
我知道我过分了
I know I went too far.
我知道的
I know I did.
这只是个游戏
It was just a game.
愚蠢的游戏
A stupid game.
-我知道它过分了  -不
- I know it went too far. - No.
你必须去  这样才能好起来
You have to go there so you can get better.
如果她不去  里奇就会跟她离婚
And if she won't go, Richie wants a divorce.
只去七个月
It's just seven months.
把合同签了吧  亲爱的
So sign the paper, sweetie.
里奇伍德精神病院
很好
Good.
这才是乖女孩
That's a good girl.
我们这就走吗
Are we going now?
是的  你要不要收拾点什么
Yeah. Hey, you want to get some things together?
-好的  跟我来  -好
- Yeah, come with me. - Yeah.
-跟我来  来吧  -你去吧  去吧
- Come with me. Come. - There you go. Go ahead.
亲爱的  把订婚戒指和手表给我
Oh, honey. Give me your engagement ring and your watch.
我们会好好保管的
We'll take good care of them.
我们真的该走了  他们  他们在等我们
We really should go. They're, they're waiting for us.
我忘带充电器了  它在我房间里
I forgot my charger. It's in my room somewhere.
过去你就用不上手机了
Oh, you're not gonna need your phone there.
我想用  手机上有我的游戏
I want my phone. It's got my games on it.
-好吧  我去拿  -我自己去
- Okay, I can go get it. - I'll get it.
我不是婴儿
I'm not a baby.
-她在哪  -厕所
- Where is she? - Bathroom.
没问题  我检查过
It's okay. I checked it.
拜托  拜托  快来
Oh, please. Please, come on.
快来  快来  快来  快来
Come on, come on, come on. Come on.
-亨特  -亨特
- Hunter! - Hunter!
-天啊  -亨特
- God. - Hunter.
把门打开
Open the door.
亨特
Hunter!
-天啊  好吧  -亨特
- Oh, God. Okay. - Hunter!
快点  闪开  闪开
Come on. Move, move!
亨特
Hunter!
-该死  -你能行吗
- Oh, goddamn it. - You got it?
亨特
Hunter?
-天啊  我们走吧  -操
- Oh, God. Here we go. - Shit!
等等  拜托  停下  停下
Hey, please! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
亨特
Hunter!
来  开我的车
Here, take my car.
停下  拜托  停下
Stop. Please, stop.
停吧  拜托  别那么混蛋
Come on, please don't be a jerk.
停车  等等  停下  停下
Come on! Hey, stop! Stop! Stop!
你好
Hi. Oh!
-谢谢你  -不用谢
- Thank you! - Sure.
-谢谢你  -你要去哪
- Thank you! - Where are you going?
西岸
\h汽车旅馆
你在哪
Ah! Where are you?
我只是想告诉你
I just wanted to explain.
我依然爱你  只是
I still have feelings for you, and..
只是
And..
我想让你幸福  可这一切对我来说太快了
I think I rushed into some stuff to make you happy..
比如我们住的地方和
...like where we live and..
这个孩子
...the baby.
-我想让你幸福  -不  不  听着
- I wanted to make you happy.. - No. No, look.
-我只是  -停  停
- And I just.. - Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
听着就行  好吗
Just listen, okay?
我真的  真的想你
I really, really miss you.
我想念我们在一起
I miss us.
你知道的  我
You know, I've been..
我希望一切能回到
I -- I want things to go back
以前那样
the way it used to be.
回来吧
Just come back.
我发誓  一切都会不一样的
I swear, things are -- are gonna be different.
你想去哪我们就去哪  只要你
We can go anywhere that you want to. Just..
我爱你
I love you.
我也想你
I miss you, too.
那就回来吧
So come back.
不
No.
我不能
I can't.
所以你要做什么  你要
So what are you gonna do? You gonna..
你要睡大街吗
You gonna live on the street?
你什么都做不好
You're not good at anything.
你什么都做不了
You can't do anything.
你只能回来
This is it.
这就是你能过上的最好的生活
This is the best it is ever going to get.
回来吧
Come back.
你自己回来  还是我来把你抓回来
You come back or I will hunt you down.
我他妈会把你抓回来的  没良心的婊子
I'll fucking hunt you down, you ungrateful cunt.
好吧  我要挂了
Okay. I have to go.
带着我的孩子回来
You get back here with my kid!
珍惜微小的东西
Treasure the little things.
我们火车上见
I'll meet you on the train.
不  我不去
No. I'm not going.
你他妈在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
等吗  等什么
Wait? Wait for what?
等一个征兆
For a sign.
我们周围全是征兆
There are signs all around us
它们藏在木制品里
hidden in the woodwork.
只要你知道去哪找
You just have to know where to look.
它就会告诉你你该做什么
It'll tell you what you do
告诉你你是谁
it'll tell you who you are.
我这辈子从没听过这么荒唐的话
I've never heard of anything so ludicrous in all my life.
好吧  你继续  想留就留下来吧
Well, go on. Stay here if you want.
只要你想  在这坐一辈子也行
Sit here the rest of your life if you want to.
我要去坐火车了
I'm getting on that train.
不用了  谢谢你  我要退房了
No, thank you. I'm checking out.
你好  妈妈  过得好吗
Hi, mom. What's up?
你好  亲爱的  听到你的声音真高兴
Hi, honey. Nice to hear your voice.
听着
Uh...listen.
我得来见你
I need to come see you.
有点急事
It's kind of an emergency.
当然
Of course.
我很高兴我们能一起住一段时间
It'll be good for us to spend some time together.
真的吗
Really?
你愿意我来吗
You want me to?
当然  亲爱的
Sure, doll.
我永远欢迎你
You're always welcome.
只是你妹妹带着新生宝宝过来了
It's just your sister's here with the new baby
我这有点住不下
and it's a little bit crowded.
拜托
Please?
我不会碍手碍脚的
I won't get in the way.
真的住不下  亲爱的
There's just no room, doll.
♪ 为了你的妈妈  你最好坚强起来 ♪
♪ You better get up for your mama ♪
-你一定要上来  -你不会想
- You got to get up there. - You don't wanna..
生日快乐
♪ 过上最好的生活 ♪
♪ ...grab the best of your life ♪
♪ 我知道你准备好了 ♪
♪ I know you're ready ♪
♪ 长大吧 ♪
♪ To get older ♪
♪ 无论如何 ♪
♪ Anyhow ♪
生日
快乐
欧文
♪ 你要做的只有 ♪
♪ Well all you have to do.. ♪
一  二  三
One, two, three.
切
Here we go.
真棒
Yay. It's great.
-好了  -真好
- Okay. - That's beautiful.
简直完美
That's truly spectacular.
干得好
Nice job.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你有一双和你女儿一样的眼睛
You have your daughter's eyes.
不  她继承了我妻子的
No, she has my wife's eyes.
我的眼睛是淡褐色的
My eyes are hazel.
我的也是
So are mine.
我们是不是以前见过
We've met before, haven't we?
我记得你的面孔  但我不确定
I know your face, but I can't place it.
-看来我们得多拿点儿潘趣酒  -好
- Oh, we need a bit more punch. - Oh.
哦  你好  我很抱歉
Oh, hi. I'm sorry.
我叫露西  你呢
I'm Lucy. What's your name?
亨特
Hunter.
你好  我是威廉
Hi, I'm William.
大家都叫我欧文
Uh, everybody calls me Erwin.
所以哪个是你的孩子
So which one of these kids is yours?
都不是  但我  我就快要有了
None of them, but I --I'm gonna have a baby soon.
-我怀孕了  -哦  恭喜
- I'm pregnant. - Oh. Congratulations!
那太好了
That's wonderful!
我  我能帮你拿点儿吗
Can I.. Can I help you with some of this?
-不  不  不  -哦  不  不  不用了
- No, no, no. - Oh, no, no, no.
就  就是
It's just, you know..
不用  没关系的  你不必强求自己
No, that's okay. You don't have to.
这是我的荣幸
It's my pleasure.
真的  你真不必如此的
Oh, you really don't have to do that.
一点也不麻烦
It's no trouble at all.
-啊  是的  -好的
- Ah.. Yep. - Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
所以  亨特  谁邀请你来派对的
So Hunter, who invited you to the party?
我  我
I, uh.. I..
你还记得吉尔·麦科伊  对不对
You remember Jill McCoy, right?
她是我母亲
She's my mom.
露西  你这有回收桶或者类似的东西吗
Lucy, do you have a recycling bin or something?
当然  我来拿吧  就在水槽底下
Oh, yeah. I'll take those. It's under the sink.
抱歉  吉尔  什么来着
I'm sorry. Jill who?
麦科伊
McCoy
她是我的一个老朋友
She's an old friend of mine.
我  好吧  我已经有年头没见她了
I.. Well, I haven't seen her in years.
嘿  布拉特  不如和你朋友一起去玩玩
Hey, Brat. Why don't you go and play with your pals.
你从没提起过关于吉尔的事情
Oh, you never mentioned any Jill.
-吉尔  -哦对  她  怎么说呢
- Jill. - Oh! Yeah. She, uh, she..
我  她母亲  我和她上同一所高中
I, her mom, I went to high school with her.
是啊  我想起来了
Yeah. Coming back to me now.
我上周碰到她了
I ran into Jill last week.
她说她的女儿  可能
She said that her daughter, uh, might
可能会顺便在派对上待会儿
you know, stop by the party.
确切的说  她和她女儿
Or rather, she and her daughter.
所以我猜你母亲没能来是吧
So I guess your mom couldn't make it, huh?
是的
No.
没来  她有点事
No, she got held up.
所以  你想喝点什么
So, so, what do you want?
苏打汽水  还是潘  潘趣酒
Um, soda? You want p -- punch?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我还没想好
I haven't decided yet.
我能带亨特看看我的房间吗
Can I show Hunter my room?
不  不  亲爱的
No. No, honey.
你得去睡觉了记得吗  过点了
You gotta go to bed. It's past your bedtime.
来吧  到这来
Oh, come on. Here.
你看着点烤架  好吗
And you're in charge of the grill, okay?
-行  没问题  -我们需要汉堡和热狗
- Okay. Yeah. Alright. - We need burgers and hot dogs.
好的  没问题  宝贝
Okay. Sure, babe.
所以
So..
你现在是要毁掉我的生活还是怎样
...are you gonna ruin my life or what?
我还没决定好
I haven't decided yet.
我猜我应该毁了你  是不是
I guess I should, right?
-别碰我  -小点声
- Don't touch me! - Keep your voice down.
我想做什么就做什么
I will do whatever the fuck I want!
在这里我制定规则
I make the rules here.
这儿现在我说了算  懂吗
I'm in charge, okay?
说出来
Say it.
说呀
好的  你说了算
Okay. You're in charge.
嘿  汉堡还没好吗  我们都饿了
Hey, where are those burgers? We're famished.
收到
Roger that!
-我们就在外面  孩子们  -没问题
- Join us outside, kids. - Yeah.
不  我们再在这待会儿  我们只是
No, we'll be there in a minute. We're just.. Just..
-能给我们几分钟时间吗  -没问题
- Can you give us a minute? - Okay.
好了  没事了
Okay. We're good.
你为什么要那么做
Why'd you do it?
我没法解释  那是因为
I can't explain that. That's..
我当时痴心妄想了  我想说
I was delusional. I mean
那根本没法解释
there's no way to explain that.
我  我当时
I -- I was..
那让我感觉我很特别
It made me feel special.
一个能让你变得强大的诀窍  懂吗
A secret makes you strong, you know?
每个人都认为我就是个平平无奇的人
Everybody thought I was this regular guy, you know
但其实我也可以被人重视
but I was important inside.
我可以无所不能
I was fucking powerful.
我就是上帝
I was God.
然后
And, um..
然后我就去了监狱
...and then I went to jail
在监狱我遭到了非人的对待
and I got shit-bagged in jail.
是啊  他们把我打的那么严重
Yeah, they beat me so bad
我不得不用上肛门袋
I had to wear a colostomy bag
然后我才意识到我是谁
and then I realized who I was.
我并不是什么上帝
I was not God.
我就是一坨屎
I was shit.
你会因我的存在而羞耻吗
Are you ashamed of me?
不会
No.
但是我以前的所作所为
But what I did..
我为那感到羞耻
...I'm ashamed of that.
我会跟你一样吗
Am I like you?
我不知道
I don't know.
你是吗
Are you?
不
No.
但是我只是需要听你说出来
But I just need to hear you say it.
你不是我
You're not me.
你
You..
你没有做任何事
You didn't do anything.
你没有做错任何事
You didn't do anything wrong.
那不是你的错
It's not your fault.
在这吃一片药
Take one pill here
等个24小时
wait 24 hours..
然后再在嘴里含四片药
...then place the remaining four pills in your mouth
腮帮子一边各俩
two in each cheek.
等待它们溶解  然后吞咽掉残留的
Wait for them to dissolve, then swallow the remnants.
♪ 我一直在守望着 ♪
♪ I've been watching ♪
♪ 我一直在游荡着 ♪
♪ I've been wandering ♪
♪ 我们一直铆着劲 ♪
♪ We've been saving up ♪
♪ 我们一直成长着 ♪
♪ We've been growing up ♪
♪ 漫漫长路我们有多少的离与别 ♪
♪ And how many friends have we lost along the way? ♪
♪ 虽然他们仍在 ♪
♪ They are still in this world ♪
♪ 但早已与我分道扬镳 ♪
♪ But not living the same ♪
♪ 我们人各有志 ♪
♪ And we'll hold to our dreams ♪
♪ 我们轻不言弃 ♪
♪ We won't give them away ♪
♪ 我们只是一遍又一遍 ♪
♪ We'll just try and we'll try ♪
♪ 一遍又一遍的尝试 ♪
♪ And we'll try and we'll try again ♪
♪ 只是一直哼着 ♪
♪ We'll just keep on singing ♪
♪ 如果你问我 ♪
♪ If you ask me ♪
♪ 我会告诉你 ♪
♪ I can tell you ♪
♪ 如果我现在变强了 ♪
♪ If I was stronger now ♪
♪ 我会离开有你的生活 ♪
♪ I would leave your life ♪
♪ 因为我们都想的是 ♪
♪ Cause all that we want ♪
♪ 一路走来有爱在陪伴 ♪
♪ Is to love along the way ♪
♪ 当我想去改变的时候 ♪
♪ There are times in this life ♪
♪ 一生会有无数的机遇 ♪
♪ When I'm willing to change ♪
♪ 如果不问你便不会动摇 ♪
♪ If you don't ask you won't budge ♪
♪ 那我们就不会离去 ♪
♪ Then we won't go away
♪ 我们只是一遍又一遍 ♪
♪ We'll just try and we'll try and we'll try ♪
♪ 一遍又一遍的尝试 ♪
♪ And we'll try and again ♪
♪ 我们会一直歌唱着 ♪
♪ We'll just keep on singing ♪
♪ 我已经学到了很多 ♪
♪ I have learned some things ♪
♪ 保持健康吧 ♪
♪ Stay healthy ♪
♪ 和你爱的人待在一起吧 ♪
♪ Be with the ones you love ♪
♪ 做你爱做的事情吧 ♪
♪ Do the things you love ♪
♪ 哦如果你问我 ♪
♪ And oh if you ask me ♪
♪ 我会告诉你 ♪
♪ I can tell you ♪
♪ 如果你问到我 ♪
♪ If you ask me ♪
♪ 努力尝试吧 ♪
♪ Keep trying ♪
♪ 我们会取得突破 ♪
♪ We will break through ♪
♪ 你知道的我们会取得突破 ♪
♪ You know we will break through ♪
♪ 因为我们只想让爱永恒 ♪
♪ Cause all that we want is to give our love away ♪
♪ 这一世我们有大把时间去改变 ♪
♪ There are times in this life we are willing to change ♪
♪ 我们会请求这个世界 ♪
♪ We will ask for the world ♪
♪ 我们将请求这个世界 ♪
♪ 我们总是一次又一次 ♪
♪ And we'll try and we'll try and we'll try ♪
♪ 一次又一次不停地在尝试 ♪
♪ And we'll try and again ♪
♪ 只是一直在哼着 ♪
♪ We'll just keep on singing ♪